

Stella Williams

INSTRUCTIONAL DESIGNER, DEVELOPER & CYBER SECURITY POSTGRADUATE STUDENT

Details

+447920461287 stella_williams@hotmail.co.uk

Links

<u>Linkedin</u> <u>Github</u>

Portfolio

Graphics

Skills

HTML

SQL

Python

Adobe InDesign

Articulate Storyline

Instructional Design

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe Photoshop

Project Management

Camtasia

JavaScript

HTML/CSS

Java

Android Studio

Figma

C/C++

Hobbies

Playing drums, making music with my band, running, cycling, swimming, hiking, and drawing.

Profile

Passionate and experienced Instructional Designer with a multifaceted background in graphic design, web development, and analytical chemistry. Adept at collaborating with designers and other team professionals to achieve high goals and deadlines. Bringing forth a commitment to creating effective, educational, and impact designs that enhance student experience.

Employment History

Senior Instructional Designer, Kaplan International, Edinburgh

II II V 2021

- Assisting management with day-to-day tasks to ensure organisation and productivity.
- Video & Audio editing expert.
- Creating designs using Adobe suite, Camtasia and Articulate 360.
- Experience with SCORM.
- Handling communication between clients and the other Instructional Designers.
- Meeting clients, academics, and stakeholders for regular meetings.
- Edited many voice-over projects for lecturecasts and informational videos.
- Working with subject matter experts and identifying the target audience's training needs.
- Skilled in using HTML and CSS.
- Server maintenance.
- Working as a trained mental health first aider to help colleagues in crisis/prevent a crisis.
- Technical writing experience.

Graphic Designer, Self-Employed, Edinburgh

JULY 2017

- Delivered visually compelling animations and graphic elements.
- Utilised Adobe Creative Suite and other 3D applications to create advanced designs and animations.
- Created and executed graphics in After Effects and Illustrator.

Analytical Chemist, Scottish Water, Edinburgh

JULY 2017 - AUGUST 2018

- Accurately interpreted laboratory results and made decisions accordingly.
- Brought forth an in-depth knowledge of routine laboratory equipment.
 Reviewed lab results to determine the best course of action for clients.
- Performed lab assessments of water samples.
- Worked in cooperation with the Senior Technologist to manage the lab and assign workloads.

Pharmacy Technician, Self Employed, Edinburgh

JULY 2018 - JUNE 2021

- Verified prescriptions prior to fulfilling orders.
- Reviewed prescriptions and maintained accurate patient records.
- Worked to promote a smooth-running Pharmacy department.
- Utilised a strong working knowledge of health and science.
- Remained up to date with new medications and field advancements.
- Remained flexible, adaptable, and punctual.

Languages

English

Portuguese

German

Education

MSc Cyber Security, University of Essex, Edinburgh

SEPTEMBER 2022 - PRESENT

- Studying secure software development, focusing on python.
- Database development.
- How to incorporate secure software design into everyday life.
- Cybercrime and law.

Web Design and Development, Napier University, Edinburgh

SEPTEMBER 2020 - JULY 2022

Completed Higher National Diploma (HND), two years.

Chemistry, Heriot-Watt University, Edinburgh

SEPTEMBER 2013 - JULY 2017

Completed BSc with Honours (4 Year Degree).

Courses

Adobe Illustrator, Udemy

DECEMBER 2021 - PRESENT

JavaScript, Udemy

JULY 2020 - OCTOBER 2020

Mental Health First Aid, MHFA England

NOVEMBER 2022 - NOVEMBER 2022

Extra-curricular activities

Secretary, ENUSEC, Edinburgh

 $\mathsf{SEPTEMBER}\ 2021-\mathsf{JUNE}\ 2022$

Edinburgh Napier University Security Society (ENUSEC) is a student society interested in all aspects of security. The society was started in 2015 by a small collective of students and staff associated with the excellent cybersecurity courses at Edinburgh Napier University. The goal of the society was, and still is, to provide the students and surrounding cybersecurity practitioners with an outlet for them further their learning and understanding as well as to foster a friendly community. I was the secretary for the society which meant leading meetings, organising events such as conferences and hackathons, and holding AGMs.

References

Conrad Hercberg from Kaplan International

conrad.hercberg@kaplan.com

David Brazier from Napier University

D.Brazier@napier.ac.uk | +44 131 455 2723